Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Communist and Socialist Serials TAM.747
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: International Publications, 1850-2013; cuid11440; 52.6 Linear Feet in 89 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 47 flat boxes
  - Subseries II.B: Other International Publications, 1850-2013; 52.6 Linear Feet in 89 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 47 flat boxes
    - Etudes Marxistes (supplement): Bloch, G./Marxistes Etudes, 1968-1969; cuid12755 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Bolshevik Newsletter: Bolshevik Club, Wellington, New Zealand, 1997; cuid12756 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - August Struggle and Its Significance: Bolshevik Leninist party of India, Bombay, India, 1947; cuid12757 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Trotskyist Bulletin: Bolshevik Tendency, Oakland, CA, 1984, 1988, 1996; cuid12758 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Marxism and Science: Bolshevik-Samasamaja Publication, Ceylon, UK/Sri Lanka, 1949; cuid12759 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - East & West: British Asian Socialist Fellowship, London, England, 1955; cuid12760 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Economic Brief: British Labour Party, London, England, 1969; cuid12761 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - 4 Discours et un programme: Cahiers Rouges, Paris, France, 1937; cuid12762 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Canada-USSR Association Bulletin: Canada-USSR Association, Toronto, Ontarion, Canada, 1963; cuid12763 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Forge: Canadian Communist League (M-L), Montreal, Canada, 1975-1976, 1979; cuid12764 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Canadian Revolution: An Independent Journal of Marxism-Leninism: Canadian Workers Press, Toronto, Canada, 1975-1976; cuid12765 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Blatter fur Religiosen Sozialismus: Carl Mennicke, Berlin, Germany, 1922-1926; cuid12766 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Cronologia del Movimiento Obrero y de las Luchas por la Revolucion Socialista en America Latina (1850-1916): Casa de las Americas, Havana, Cuba, 1979; cuid12767 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Gramma: Central Committee of the Communist Party of Cuba, Havana, Cuba, 1975 (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Gramma International: Central Committee of the Communist Party of Cuba, Havana, Cuba, 1993, 2002-2003; cuid12768 (Box 27, Folder 3-4, Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Gramma: 20th Anniversary: Central Committee of the Communist Party of Cuba, Havana, Cuba, 1973; cuid12769 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Gramma: Weekly Review: Central Committee of the Communist Party of Cuba, Havana, Cuba, 1969, 1973-1976, 1978-1980, 1983-1984, 1986-1990; cuid12770 (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
    - Ang Bayan: Central Committee of the Communist Party of the Philippines, 1972; cuid12771 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Ang Bayan: Central Committee of the Communist Party of the Philippines, Philippines, 1971-1972 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Bolshevik / Bolchevique: Central Committee of the Leninist Core for the Revolutionary League, Bronx, NY, 1976-1978; cuid12772 (Box 23, Folder 20-21)
    - Information Bulletin of the People's Youth of Yugoslavia: Central Committee of the People's Youth of Yugoslavia, Belgrade, Serbia, 1949; cuid12773 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Information Bulletin: Central Committee of the Polish United Workers' Party, Warsaw, Poland, 1987; cuid12774 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Spartacist Britain: Central Committee Spartacist League, London, England, 1978, 2004, 2007; cuid12775 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Vanguardia obrera: Central de Trabajadores de Cuba, Havana, Cuba, 1966; cuid12776 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - L'unite: central du parti d'unite proletarienne, paris, france, 1934; cuid12777 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Socialist Alternatives: Centre for Developing Area Studies, McGill University, Montreal, Canada, 1991-1993; cuid12778 (Box 14, Folder 1-6)
    - Los Paises Socialistas en la Historia Contemporanea: Centro de Estudios, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1972; cuid12779 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Ventesimo Secolo: Centro Ligure di Storia Sociale, Milan, Italy, 1991-1992 (Box 247, Folder 9-11)
    - Chartist: Bulletin of the Young Chartists: The Chartist, Northolt Park, England, Undated (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Chartist International: Chartist publications, London, England, 1974; cuid12780 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Antidote: Class Action, Toronto, Ontario, Canada, 2001; cuid12781 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Class War: Class War, Edinburgh, Scotland/New York, NY, 1995; cuid12782 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - International Bulletin: CLO, 1932-1933; cuid12783 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Collettivo CR: Collettivo, CR, Torino, Italy, 1970; cuid12784 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Decimo Congreso: Comision Nacional de Propaganda del partido comunista de Colombia, 1966; cuid12785 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Trinchera Aprista: Comité Aprista de México, Mexico, 1938; cuid12786 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Boletin: Comite Central de la Izquierda Comunista, Chile, 1933; cuid12787 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Bulletin d'Information et de Presse du Comite pour l'Enquete sur le Proces de Moscou: Comité Central de la Ligue des Droits de l'Homme et à la Ligue, Paris, France, circa 1950s; cuid12788 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Tribuna Popular: Comite Central del Partido Comunista de Venezuela, Caracas, Venezuela, 1981 (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Combatiente: por la revolución mexicana al socialismo: Comite Central del Partido Popular Socialista, Mexico City, Mexico, 1979-1980, 1987; cuid12789 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Cahiers du Communisme (Special): Comite Central du Parti Communiste Francais, Paris, France, 1961 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - La Verdad: Comite Comunista de Oposicion, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1930; cuid12790 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Communique du Comite de defense sociale: Comite de Defense sociale, Paris, France, circa 1960s; cuid12791 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - La Commune: Comite de Liaison et d' Action pour la democratie ouvriere, Paris, France, 1958; cuid12792 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Boletin Informataivo del Comite Central del Partido Comuista de Chile: Comite Central del Partido Comunista de Chile, Chile, 1972 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Accion: Comite Departamental del Sena del P.S.O.E., Paris, France, 1966; cuid12793 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Debat sur la crise ud stalinisme: Comite d'organisation pour la reconstruction de la Quatrieme Internationale, Paris, France, 1978; cuid12794 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Quatrième Internationale: Comite Executif International de la IVe Internationale, Paris, France, 1936, 1938, 1944-1950, 1953, 1963, 1966, 1968-1975, 1980-1985; cuid12795 (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
    - Conference Socialiste Internationale: Comite Organisateur de la Conference Socialiste Internationale de Stockholm, Stockholm, Sweden, 1918 (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Bulletin International des Jeunesses Bolcheviks-Leninistes: Commission Centrale Internationale des Jeunes Pres, Brusells, Belgium, 1934; cuid12796 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Working People: Committee for a Socialist Program, London, England, 1975; cuid12797 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Unsere Zeit: UZ; sozialistische Wochenzeitung; Zeitung der DKP: CommPress-Verl., Essen, Germany, 2007; cuid12798 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Le Proletaire: Communisme Revolutionnaire, Lyon, France, 1946; cuid12799 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Marxist Leninist Quarterly: Communist Federation of Britain (Marxist-Leninist), London, England, 1973; cuid12800 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Bibliothek der Kommunistischen Internationale: Communist International, Hamburg, Germany, 1920-1922; cuid12801 (Box 16, Folder 3-5)
    - Jahrbuch fur politik wirtschaft arbeiterbewegung: communist international, Hamburg, Germany, 1922; cuid12802 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - La Lutte Ouvriere: Communist International, Brussels, Belgium, 1936-1939, 1945-1947; cuid12803 (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
    - Spartacus: Communist International, Belgium, 1935-1936; cuid12804 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - IV International: Communist International League, Mexico, 1936-1938; cuid12805 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Compass Communist League: Communist League, Essex, England, 1995; cuid12806 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - La Lutte de Classes: Communist League, Paris, France, 1932; cuid12807 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Der Apikoyres: Communist League of America, 1934; cuid12808 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - 2nd Conference of Groups of the Communist Left: Communist Left, Paris, France, 1978 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - La Liberte: Communist Party, Paris, France, 1937 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Marxism Today: Theoretical and Discussion Journal of the Communist Party: Communist Party (Great Britain)/Farleigh Press Ltd., London, England, 1969, 1973, 1976; cuid12809 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Vanguard: Communist Party of Australia, Coburg, Australia, 1967-1968; cuid12810 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - People's Canada Daily News Service: Communist Party of Canada (Marxist-Leninist), Toronto, Canada, 1972; cuid12811 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Resolutions of Enlarged Plenum of Communist Party of Canada: Communist Party of Canada, Toronto, Ontario, 1931 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Communist Unity Convention: Communist Party of Great Britain, London, England, 1920 (Box 248, Folder 18)
    - Fourth Congress of the Communist International: Abridged Report: Communist Party of Great Britain/Communist International, London, England, 1922 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Resolutions and Theses of the Fourth Congress of the Communist International: Communist Party of Great Britain / Communist International, London, England, 1922 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Party Life - Inter-Party Journal of Organisation Department: Communist Party of India, New Delhi, India, 1969; cuid12812 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Irish Socialist: Communist Party of Ireland, Dublin, Ireland, 1976; cuid12813 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Unity: Communist Party of Ireland (Northern Area), Belfast, Ireland, 1976; cuid12814 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Unity: Communist Party of Ireland, Dublin, Ireland, 1994, 1995, 1998; cuid13376 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - Information Bulletin: Communist Party of Israel, Tel-Aviv, Israel, 1973-1974, 1976, 1979, 1984, 1987, 1989; cuid12815 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Information Bulletin: Communist Party of Israel Central Committee, Tel Aviv, Israel, 1971; cuid12816 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Focus: Communist Party Weekly: Focus, London, England, 1985; cuid12871 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Seventh World Congress Proceedings: Communist Party USA, Vienna, Austria, 1935-1936; cuid12817 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Workers Voice: Communist Workers Association, Glasgow, Scotland, 1981; cuid12818 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Workers' Notebook: Communist Workers Movement, Liverpool, England, 1977; cuid12819 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Le Bolchevik: Communiste Internationale (Quatrieme-Internationaliste), Paris, France, 2000-2002; cuid12820 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Proletarian Line: Communist Revolutionaries of India, Hyderabad, India, 1980; cuid12821 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Boletin Interior de Discusion: Comunista Internacionalista, 1933, 1948-1949; cuid12822 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Le Peuple: Confederation Generale du Travail, Paris, France, 1954; cuid13352 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Capital & Class: Conference of Socialist Economists, London, England, 1977-1993 (Box 220, Folder 6, Box 221, Folder 1-4)
    - CSE Newsletter: Conference of Socialist Economics, London, England, 1979-1980; cuid12823 (Box 17, Folder 7, Box 224)
    - Conference of Socialist Economists Newsletter: Conference of Socialist Economists, London, England, 1977; cuid12824 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Ce Qu'est devenue la Revolution Russe: Cooperative Ouvriere Egitna, Paris, France, circa 1960s; cuid12825 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Boletin Liberacion: Coordinating Committee of the Communist Youth of Chile Abroad, Berlin, Germany, 1976; cuid13378 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - American Labour: Counselor for Labor Affairs, American Embassy, New Dheli, India, 1969; cuid12826 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Revue Internationale: Courant Communiste International, Paris, France, 1979-1981; cuid12827 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Rupture avec Lutte Ouvriere et le Trotskyme: Courant Communiste International, Paris, France, 1976; cuid12828 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Revolution Internationale: Courant Communiste International en France, Paris, France, 1977; cuid12829 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Revolution International: Courant Comuniste International, Paris, France, 1979-1981; cuid12830 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - News and Views: CPGB, London, England, 1988; cuid12831 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Tribuna del Decimo Congreso: Decimo Congreso Nacional del Partido Comunista de Colombia, 1976; cuid12832 (Box 17, Folder 13, Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Democrat: Democrat, Vancouver, BC, Canada, 1990; cuid12833 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Mitteilungen: der Marxistischen Aktion der Schweiz, Zurich, Switzerland, 1936; cuid12834 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Befreiung der Menichheit: Deutches Berlagshaus Bong & Co., 1921; cuid12835 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Diskussions Material: Die Krise der Vierten Internationale, 1946; cuid12836 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Der I. und II. Kongres der Kommunistischen Internationale: Dietz Verlag Berlin, Berlin, Germany, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - de AS: driebergen, Netherlands, 1992; cuid12837 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - International Socialist review: E. Grant, London, England, 1972; cuid12838 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Workers Opposition: E. Morse, Reading, England, 1960; cuid12839 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Bulletin of the International Institute of Social History Amsterdam: E.J. Brill, Amsterdam, Holland, 1952-1955; cuid12840 (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
    - East European Reporter: East European Reporter, london, england, 1987; cuid12841 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Impression of Russia: Economist, London, England, 1930; cuid12842 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Pravda: ed. Borin, V.L., London, England, 1951; cuid12843 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - USSR News Brief: Human Rights: Ed: Cronid Lubarsky, Munich, Germany, 1989; cuid12844 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Las Ideas Antisocialistas de Teodoro Petkoff: Ediciones Cantaclaro, Caracas, Venezuela, 1970; cuid12845 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Pabellon: Ediciones Pabellon, Guaynabo, Puerto Rico, 1965; cuid12846 (Box 17, Folder 20, Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Conferencia de los Partidos Comunistas de America Latina y del Caribe: Ediciones Politicas, Havana, Cuba, 1975; cuid12847 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Critique Communiste: Editions la Breche, Paris, France, 1976, 1978, 1981, 1982; cuid12848 (Box 25, Folder 4-6)
    - Les Congres de la Quatrieme Internationale: Editions la Breche, Paris, France, 1978, 1981; cuid12849 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - L'homme etla societe: editions l'harmattan, Paris, France, 1990, 1992; cuid12850 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
    - Bibliothèque Marxiste: Editions Sociales Intenationales, Paris, France, 1933; cuid12851 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Informe del Comite Central Presentado por el Jesus Faria al V Congresso del PCV: Editorial "Rio Orinoco, CA"/Partido Comunista de Venezuela, Caracas, Venezuela, 1974; cuid12852 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Programa del Partido Comunista de Venezuela: Editorial "Rio Orinoco, CA"/Partido Comunista de Venezuela, Caracas, Venezuela, 1974; cuid12853 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Un Deslinde Necesario: Editorial Arte y Literatura, Havana, Cuba, 1976; cuid12854 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Juventud y Polemica: Editorial Cantaclaro, Caracas, Venezuela, 1970; cuid12855 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Vida política de mi patria: cuaderno de trabajo: cuarto grado: Editorial Pueblo y Educacion, Havana, Cuba, 1978; cuid12856 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - ?Liberalismo o Sodialismo?: Editorial Sigma, Pereira, Colombia, circa 1940s; cuid12857 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Revolucion Proletaria: El Pueblo Trabajador, Havana, Cuba, 1945; cuid12858 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Bulletin d'Information et de Discussion: Europe Bolchevik-Leniniste de la Federation, 1935 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence of the Young International: Executive Committee of the Communist Young International, Berlin, Germany, 1922-1923; cuid12859 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - International Correspondence: Executive Committee of the International Committee of the Fourth International, London, England, 1967; cuid12860 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Jugend-Internationale: Exekutiv-Comitee der Kommunistischen Jugendinternationale, Berlin, Germany, 1928; cuid12861 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
    - Völkischer Beobachter: F. Eher Nachf., Berlin, Germany, 1933; cuid12862 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Fabian Journal: Fabian Publications Ltd., London, England, 1955; cuid12863 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Fabian Society: Fabian Society, London, England, 1989; cuid12864 (Box 26, Folder 10, Box 227, Folder 7)
    - Fabian Society - assorted reports: Fabian Society, London, England, circa 1980s; cuid12865 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Fabian Society Briefing: Fabian Society, London, England, 1988; cuid12866 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Fabian Society Discussion Paper: Fabian Society, London, England, 1996; cuid12867 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Facts for Socialists: Fabian Society, London, England, 1991; cuid12868 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - L'Étudiant révolutionnaire: organe de la Fédération des Étudiants Révolutionnaires: Fédération des Étudiants Révolutionnaires, Paris, France, 1968; cuid12869 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Revolution: Federation des Jeunesses Socialistes Revolulionnaires (IVe Internationale), Paris, France, 1936-1939; cuid12870 (Box 57, Folder 4, Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Mao Tsetung (Statement): Foreign Language Press, Peking, China, 1970; cuid12872 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Lenin on the National and Colonial Questions: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1970; cuid12873 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Lu Hsun: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1975; cuid12874 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Manifesto of the Communist Party: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1969; cuid12875 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Mao Tse-tung on Strengthening the Party Committee System: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1967; cuid12876 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Mao Tse-Tung: On the Correct Handling of Contradictions Among the People: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1960; cuid12877 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Mao Tse-Tung: Reform our Study: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1965; cuid12878 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Mao Tse-Tung: the Orientation of the Youth Movement: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1960; cuid12879 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - On Khrushchov's Phoney Communism and its Historical lessons for the World: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1964; cuid12880 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Problems of Agrarian Policy in the U.S.S.R.: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, circa 1950s; cuid12881 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Summary on the Fourm on the Work in Literaure and Art in the Armed Forces with which Comrade Lin Piao Entrusted Comrade Chiang Ching: Foreign Languages Press, Peking, China, 1968; cuid12882 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Chongsan-Ri Today: Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, DPRK, 1970; cuid12883 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Documents of the Fourth Congress of the Workers' Party of Korea: Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Democratic People's Republic of Korea, 1961 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Kim Il Sung: Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea, 1973; cuid12884 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Kim Il Sung: Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea, 1978; cuid12885 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Third Congress of the Workers' Party of Korea: Documents and Materials: Foreign Languages Publishing House, Pyongyang, Korea, 1956 (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Young Communist League Australia pamphlet: Forward Press LTD, Sydney, Australia, 1937; cuid12886 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Approaching a Decisive Turning Point in Gt. Britain: Fourth International, London, England, circa 1960s; cuid12887 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - La Vérité - The Truth: Fourth International, Paris, France, 1993-1995; cuid12888 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - L'Etincello: Fraction Francaise de la Gauche Communiste, France, 1945; cuid12889 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Cahiers Rouges: Documents de Formation Communiste: Francois Maspero, Paris, France, 1971; cuid12890 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Cahiers Rouges: Serie Marx ou Creve: Francois Maspero, Paris, France, 1971; cuid12891 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Classique Rouge: Serie Leon Trotsky: Francois Maspero, Paris, France, 1969; cuid12892 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Links: Frieden, Freiheit, Sozialismus Zeitschrift des Sozialistischen Deutschen Studentbundes: Frankfurt am Main: Der Bund, Frankfurt, Germany, 1953 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Information Bulletin: French Communist Party, Argenteuil, France, 1966 (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - Soziale Bewegung online: Friedrich Ebert Stiftung, Bonn, Germany, 2004; cuid12893 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Vito: Fundashon Vito, Aruba, 1970 (Box Shared Tamiment 061, Folder 13)
    - Tribuna popular: G. Machado, Caracas, Venezuela, 1993; cuid12894 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Rapport du Parti Socialiste Revolutionnaire de Russie au Congres Socialiste International de Stuttgart: Gand: Société coopérative "Volksdrukkerij", Gand, France, 1907 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Journal des Journaux de la commune: Garnier Freres, Paris, France, 1871; cuid12895 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Gay Left: Gay Left Collective, London, England, 1976; cuid12896 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Die Neue Front: German Foreign Office, Paris, France, 1933-1934; cuid12897 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Le Veteran socialiste: Groupe Nationale des Aciens du Parti Socialiste, SFIO, Paris, France, 1963; cuid12898 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Servir le Peuple: Groupes de Travail Communistes et de l'Union des Jeunesses Communistes (Marxiste-Leniniste), Paris, France, 1968; cuid12899 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Le Lien Socialiste: Groupes Socialistes de la Region Parisienne, Paris, France, 1946; cuid12900 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Comunismo: Grupo Comunista Internacionalista, Brussels, Belgium, 1991; cuid12901 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Contra la Corriente: Grupo Espanol en Mexico de la IV Internacional, 1943; cuid12902 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Grupo Internacionalista Obrero- Boletin Informativo: Grupo Internacionalista Obrero, Santiago, Chile, 1937-1938; cuid12903 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Was Tun: Gruppe Internationale Marxisten (GIM), Frankfurt, Germany, 1985; cuid12904 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Die Internationale: Gruppe Internationale Marxisten (GIM) - Deutsche Sektion der IV Internationale, 1970; cuid12905 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Die Internationale Sozialistische Konferenz in Wien: Halpern & Co., Vienna, Austria, 1921 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - The Labour Party Foundation Conference and Annual Conference Reports 1900-1905: Hammerstein Bookshop Ltd., London, England, 1967; cuid12906 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Svyazhsk: Hashim Press, Maradana, Sri Lanka, 1918; cuid12907 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Internationales Jugend-Bulletin = International Bulletin of the Youth: Herausgegeben Vom Internationalen Buro Revolutionarer Jugendorganisationen, Stockholm, Sweden, 1934; cuid12908 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - History Workshop Journal: History Workshop Journal, Oxford, England, 1976-1980; cuid12909 (Box 53, Folder 12-15, Box 55, Folder 1-5)
    - Tufan: Hizb-i Kumunist-i Kargaran va Dihqanan-i Iran, 1978 (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Internationale Jugend-Information: I.K.L., Copenhagen, Denmark, 1935; cuid12910 (Box 53, Folder 6, Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Manifesto of the Revolutionary Socialist Party, Czechoslovakia: I.M.G. Publication/International Marxist Group, Czechoslovakia, 1970; cuid13341 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - La Correspondencia Internacional: Impresos Cosmos, Valencia, Spain, 1937; cuid12911 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Les Socialistes: Imprimerie Beroud, Paris, France, 1949; cuid13337 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Avance: Imprimerie La Ruche Ouviere, Paris, France, 1971; cuid12912 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Humanité rouge: Imprimerie N.P.P, Paris, France, 1969; cuid12913 (Box 77, Folder 2)